this video. So, I am going to explain one more thing. So, the threat factors will be targeting
the MySQL servers. So, maybe you know about the MySQL. So, there are some database,
MySQL database. And it was running on the port, number 3, 3, 0, 6. So, that has been
easily compromised if the MySQL service was running under the vulnerable version, it is
an outdated version. So, that will be a very sensitive and very easy threat. We can compromise
in environment very easily. So, if the MySQL was running in the outdated version. So,
we can install on for that by searching the MySQL. Let me give some examples of how
the MySQL has been compromised. So, we are facing like 5 to 10 percent of the attacks
with us are compromising the threat factors compromising the MySQL services which was
running in the customer environment. So, some of the customer they will not update the
MySQL service. They will be still running the vulnerable versions. So, threat factors will
use the versions and they will be compromising their environment. They can execute the remote
code, malicious remote command into the MySQL servers and they get a reversal from that.
MySQL, let me give the exploit. Sorry. So, you can see a lot of reference for a MySQL
exploit. So, there is a authenticated bypass password done. And if we see MySQL recent CVE
2024, there is a lot of CVE will be there. Let us open this. So, here you can find
easily exploitable vulnerability allows high privilege attacker with the network access via
multiple protocols to compromise MySQL server. So, the attackers can be able to execute
the remote code sometime to the vulnerability. And there is a lot of lot of MySQL CVE will
be available in the environment. So, here you can find. So, if you need to search
the MySQL version, MySQL latest version. So, here you can find let us release the
send all. So, when it was released, you can you can use that information and you can get
to it. Here you can see a MySQL servers, the latest version. So, if the customers was running
in the outdated version, then it would be then the customers will be easily exploitable
by the MySQL vulnerability. So, we are facing all like 5 to 10% of our attacks through
the MySQL or MySQL services. So, this is a Microsoft SQL server and it is used for
a database management. So, here you can see how the attack will be compromising MySQL
and all, but it will be easily exploitable if it has to vulnerability.
So, the recommendations to be the customers needs, the customers needs to pass the MySQL
servers, but this video is about constant, I just focused on. So, you need to know about
the initial access. How all the ways the retention will be entered into the machine. So,
MySQL is one of the things. So, here you can find out on recent CVE 2024. So, if you read
the CVE difficult to exploit, allow low privilege attacker with the network, access via
multiple protocols to compromise MySQL. So, we can do lot of things from here. So, not only
this, there is lot of lot of CVEs will be available for MySQL. So, if the customer environment
was using the MySQL servers, you can easily exploit that. So, let me go for SQL. So, this
is one of the SQL version. So, let me see what are the customers using the SQL versions.
So, we will do one thing. So, if this is for the, okay. So, let me see which are the
users also using this 10.0, 0.60, 0.2, 9 versions. So, if the version is already exploitable,
we can exploit the MySQL services. Let me check. So, here you can find already I said the
port MySQL was a 3 3 8 6, but will be for MySQL. So, you can see a SQL server, those
we are asking running here. So, it was running on the version of 15.0.2.5. So, I have
taken some of the reference, some of the IPs from here. Let me search with that IP. So, here you can
find the port number 3 3, 0 6 was running and the 3 3 0 6 was running on the versions of Maria database.
So, the sort of not showing another interesting thing, it was showing one of the DSMD host asp in there. So, it is a
serious vulnerability. We can execute the remote code and we can take a reversal from that. So, this is another
one version. So, this hacking web comes and I will show it in later last session. There
was part of a video. But now you can find these are the custom of surrounding in the SQL
versions of SQL vulnerabilities. So, you can find 10.0. Something here and if you check the
versions SQL exploit. So, there will be a lot of vulnerabilities. So, you need to gather information
about the vulnerability and you can exploit the vulnerability and you can take a reversal from
a reversal and it goes connections from there. So, these are the few things that are
protected in the initial access to the target machines.
So, let's have a video and I will show the camera. So, here we can find the open camera
connections. So, you can see the set has a lot of vulnerabilities. So, here you can find
some photos there and something has been there. So, this is how this the Webcam XT5 and
was running properly without any use and insert passwords. You can we can see each and
everything. So, what was the things and all. So, let's have of this video and we will
continue our discussion in the next video. See you guys bye bye.